A hiker found the body of a faceless girl.
Emma has that top.
There's no match on her fingerprints.
Probably someone without an ID card
but somehow managed to live in Hong Kong.
Something must have happened to Emma.
See? Emma just texted me. She's OK.
Don't worry, your sister is fine.
I'll take you to her.
(Day 7 after Emma left)
What's wrong?
What is it?
Look at this!
Female corpse found in the New Territories.
Bodies found by hikers is nothing new.
But this time the victim's face
was chewed up by wild boars
leaving behind a bloody mess.
It was a faceless corpse.
She has the same build as Emma.
Emma has the same top. It's Emma!
(Faceless female body found in woods)
(Police conducting investigation)
Wait...no, calm down.
This footage is dark and blurry.
It also says the face of the corpse
was chewed up by wild boars.
You can't tell who it was.
How can we be sure it was Emma?
Daddy, I recognize the top.
I bought it with Emma the other day.
I really think it was her.
That top is dirty.
A lot of people have tops like that.
No...it can't be her.
Even if that wasn't Emma,
I'm sure she's in trouble.
She's been missing for so long,
I think we should call the Police.
Are you crazy? We can't.
Your sister ran away on her own.
She's not missing.
Besides, you don't have ID cards.
If we could call the Police,
I would have done it already.
Then what can we do?
Let's hire a private detective.
Maybe he can find her.
I don't feel well.
What's wrong, Mom?
I have a headache...
Mom is sick, don't provoke her.
I have a patient who is a CID.
I can ask her to find out if any ID card
was found on the body.
If they did, then it wasn't Emma.
Great! Don't forget!
Don't get ideas in your head.
Your sister is smart.
She won't get into trouble.
Mom is not well. I'll help her upstairs.
Come on...
I will protect you and Mom
and won't get you in trouble.
(The day Emma left)
Wait...you don't have your old phone,
how can I get in touch with you?
Get your phone out.
This is my new chat app.
I'll contact you on my new phone.
Though I lost the old phone,
it's OK, Daddy doesn't know the password.
He can't turn it on.
Remember this icon.
Let's use a name Daddy won't suspect.
How about... "Louise"?
OK! When we book our equestrian classes,
we contacted the coach directly.
Daddy won't suspect anything.
Remember my icon.
Don't tell Daddy I have a new phone.
If he found out, I couldn't do anything.
I'll talk to you when I'm safe.
Please don't go.
I don't want you to go.
I'll contact you, silly.
You're not scared out there on your own?
This is the first time I'm leaving home.
I don't know what the future holds.
But that won't stop me...
But I'm really scared.
Since the day I was born,
we have never been apart.
What will happen to me after you're gone?
Regardless of how much you hate Daddy,
you still have me and Mom.
I'll miss you and Mom too.
But I must go.
If I don't, I won't know what to do
with my life in the future.
Is what you want really worth
taking the risks?
I only know if I don't leave,
I'll regret it in the future.
You'll understand someday.
No matter what happens,
if you're unhappy and you need me,
you can always call me.
Wherever I am, I'll always be your sister.
Stop crying!
I really must go...
Don't blame Elsa.
I can't believe she'd run away
and took $1M with her.
She's running around with so much cash.
And God knows who she's hanging out with.
She can't go far without an ID card.
I better go find her.
I'll go with you.
I wish I had the nerve to tell Daddy
Emma has another phone.
If Emma got into an accident,
it would have been my fault.
(The night Emma left)
What should we do now?
It's dangerous for her to be
out there alone.
We've been to places she usually goes to.
It's late. She must have found
a place to stay.
We'll look again tomorrow.
What else can we do?
Still no sign of Emma?
No. We looked for her all night.
Just now, I tried to turn on her
phone and laptop.
They both require a password.
Do you know what it is?
I don't.
Does she have any friends?
Anyone she can stay with?
I really don't know.
Emma didn't say when she left.
Who is that? Is it Emma?
No...news notification.
You and Emma are very close,
she's bound to contact you.
You must tell us, OK?
I will. I'll get you some ginseng tea.
Are you worried Daddy will check my phone?
That's why you didn't make contact?
(Day 7 after Emma left)
Louise, what happened to you?
Hurry up and tell me where you are.
Why didn't you contact me?
Just call me.
If you won't, I'll look for you.
Don't change the subject.
Is he your boyfriend?
Hey!
I saw at the bar
you were quite chummy with that guy.
OK! You win.
The guy at the bar...his name is Ken.
How did you meet him? Was it romantic?
You're so nosy!
Now, you know my biggest secret.
Don't you...
Don't tell Mom and Daddy, right?
I know.
How long do you intend to
keep this from them?
I have no idea.
Daddy already hit the roof when
he found out I was at a bar.
If he knew I was dating someone, I'm dead.
I'll play it by ear.
Play by ear?
You're not serious about this guy?
Of course not. I'm dead serious.
I intend to be with him forever.
You plan to leave home
and move in with this guy?
Yes!
Is he more important than the family?
Do I have a choice? We have no ID cards.
Daddy won't even let us make friends.
Let alone date anyone.
Mom and Daddy really love us.
At home, we have everything we want.
Out there, we'd be on our own.
We don't have ID cards, we can't get a job.
You can't do anything without money.
What do I have here?
Nothing but four walls.
My dream is to venture out
and take a look at this world.
Meet more people and see more things.
After I had my adventure,
I'll come back and take you with me
so you can see the world too.
OK...out there, you'll get
anything you want.
You'll get rich
and come back so we can fly anywhere.
You learnt to be sarcastic.
When I'm happy flying out there,
and be happy with my boyfriend.
Don't be jealous, OK?
Emma will definitely contact her boyfriend.
If I can find Ken,
I'll be able to find Emma.
Emma will definitely contact her boyfriend.
If I can find Ken,
I'll be able to find Emma.
Let's try her birthday.
Maybe it's her birthday again.
Or the dates in reverse?
Wrong again?
Only three more chances left,
If I guessed wrong again,
it'll lock the account.
Take the meds and get some rest.
Stop thinking. Lie down...
Morning, Daddy!
Morning!
How is Mom?
She didn't sleep well.
I just gave her sleeping pills.
Let her sleep.
You're not eating breakfast?
No. Keep an eye on Mom, OK?
Still no answer.
How can I find Ken?
Emma must have used her old phone
to message him before.
Where did Daddy hide her phone?
Mom? Mom?
Thanks!
Hey, take your pick.
Brother Bo, getting afternoon tea again?
I'm not busy. I love getting afternoon tea.
Ling...
Yes?
The usual for me.
OK!
Let's wait for the team...
Here...two iced lemon water,
easy on the ice and syrup.
Two iced lemon tea,
three iced lemon coffee,
one tea with condensed milk.
One corned beef scrambled egg sandwich,
toasted but no edges.
These guys are so picky...
How much is it?
Brother Bo?
Where are you going?
I got you afternoon tea.
I'm on an exchange program.
Upstairs wants my personal details.
Sergeant, I'm sorry you had to get
my afternoon tea all the time.
Don't talk like that. I don't mind...
Take a break and you can think.
Hey, take your iced lemon coffee.
OK!
Get a straw!
Thanks.
Fung!
Ching Sir!
What are you working on?
The faceless corpse.
Afternoon tea...come and get it.
Perfect!
Come and get it...
Great!
Ching Sir, your iced lemon coffee...
Here, Brother Bo...
A new case...
Right.
Get someone to follow up.
Yes, Sir.
I'll be in a meeting.
Yes, Sir!
Pork chop bun...
Ching Sir!
The autopsy report of the faceless
corpse is out.
Thanks.
The report says the victim was between
22 to 25 years old.
The cause of death was internal bleeding
from liver laceration.
The medical examiner deduced she fell
from height.
Based on the degree of decomposition,
the estimated time of death was
between the 7th and the 10th of this month.
Between the 7th and the 10th?
That means when she was discovered,
she has been dead three to six days.
A pretty girl chewed up like that
by a wild boar...what a pity!
How do you know she was pretty?
Young girls are usually pretty.
A girl in her 20s can't be too ugly.
She was buried.
Then it wasn't an accident.
It's probably murder.
You're right. But the key is,
the victim didn't have any proof of identity
and her face was chewed up.
There's still no match on her fingerprints.
We still don't know who she was.
The girl's outfit was rather trendy.
Looks like she liked to party
and was probably a bar hopper.
Check that out.
Brother Bo, there are so many bars
in Hong Kong,
where should we start checking?
Her clothes are not expensive stuff.
I don't think she has any money.
Start with the cheap ones.
Especially those you don't have to pay.
Look for bars that have Ladies Night.
Those that stamp your arm and give you
free drinks all night.
But the report didn't say
there were stamps on her arm.
I'll ask the medical examiner to
double check.
No need. Just go to the morgue.
Thanks. We'll let ourselves out.
OK!
Bingo!
T Bar...
How else can I find Ken?
Yes...the bar tender at the bar
seemed quite friendly with Emma.
Maybe he knew Ken.
If I go back to that bar,
maybe I'll find him...
Mom is asleep,
Daddy is at work and won't be home soon.
This is the best time to go.
I'll go check it out.
Police! Hit the lights and kill the music.
Who's in charge?
Bars have undesirable characters
who will attract the Police.
You almost got busted today
because you don't have an ID.
The bar is full of undesirable people.
Should I go there alone?
Elsa, haven't seen you at the
library lately.
Even if you don't want to see
the concert with me,
there's no need to stay away from
the library to avoid me.
No. I need a favor.
No problem. Call me anytime.
Hello, YY!
Hello, Elsa.
Aren't we going to Tender Bar?
Yes. How should we get there?
Taxi should be the quickest.
No rush. We have time for drinks.
We're not there to drink.
I'm looking for someone.
Looking for someone?
I need to find someone.
But I seldom go to bars.
You're a reporter, you've been around.
I'd feel better if you went with me.
No problem. I'll help you any way I can.
Let me...
Thanks. I knew I came to the right person.
That's the one. Let's wait for the next one.
No. Let's go...
Wait up...hurry up!
Are you OK?
I'm fine. Thanks.
Who are you looking for? You seem uptight.
Maybe you don't want to tell me.
But if you need my help,
you should at least let me know
who you're looking for so I can help you.
Not that I don't want to tell you.
I just didn't know how.
The person I'm looking for,
is my sister's boyfriend.
His name is Ken.
But Daddy is against her dating anyone.
I figure if I check out this guy,
if he's a nice guy,
I'd help my sister put in
a good word for him.
If he's a creep, I'd tell Emma
to ditch him.
How did you know about Ken and Tender Bar?
I don't. But I went with Emma last time.
I saw him there.
I figure he must go there often.
Just ask your sister where Ken is.
I can't do that.
What if he knew I checked up on
her boyfriend secretly?
She'd think I'm meddling.
If we don't see Ken at the bar,
ask the bartender for me,
about Ken's background and personality
and who does he hang out with.
Don't forget to ask about his hangouts.
I think you should change your name.
What?
Do you know why my name is YY?
I used to ask a lot of questions
when I was little.
Why, why, why...
That's why my family called me YY.
I guess you can use my name too.
Hey...
Are you OK?
I'm fine. Thanks.
Emma said a true gentleman is rare nowadays.
You seem to be an exception.
No, I charge by the hour.
OK. I'll pay you by day.
I can make better use of you.
OK.
What are you doing?
It's clumsy carrying these around.
We'll get them later.
You're right.
You see Ken in here?
Not really...
Two gin tonics.
Sure!
Lee, right?
I'm YY.
I'm looking for Ken. You know him?
Ken? There are a few Kens in here.
Which one are you looking for?
This Ken is in his 20s.
Pointed chin and rather skinny.
Not too tall...
Can you stand up...
Shorter than he is.
Now, I remember.
This guy is bad news.
He often brings his friends in here.
But they're into different vices.
Really?
Has he been around lately?
What do you want with him?
Are you one of his many girlfriends?
What do you mean?
People like him always has his arms
around a girl.
Different girls, no less.
Tell your sister to ditch him.
Hi, Crime Unit, New Territories East.
How can I help you, Sir?
Is this the stamp you use for admittance?
Yes, that's the Tender Bar stamp.
Every Thursday night is Ladies Night.
That's the stamp we use.
Can you give us the CCTV footage
from the 1st to the 13th of this month?
Sure. Follow me.
Kwan Sir?
YY the reporter!
You have a good memory.
Please step aside...Police at work.
Excuse me...
Sorry, I'm late. What's the story?
The victim was around 30 years old.
Our initial assessment is that
he killed himself with LPG.
But before he died,
he cut off his genitals with a knife.
Using LPG to commit suicide
needs to plan ahead.
I think he completed some sort of
religious ritual.
Now this officer has good sense.
This should be the Oneness Sect.
What is the Oneness Sect?
It's a hardcore religion from overseas.
They believe suicide is not
the end of your life.
It is a means to put your soul on
a spaceship
and you can embark on a journey
into space.
Male disciples often castrate themselves
before they commit suicide
because they wish to be free from
the constraints of binary gender,
and travel through space in
a genderless state.
You knew about the Oneness Sect.
How could I forget you?
What case are you on?
Haven't you seen the news lately?
The faceless female corpse?
You're so smart.
Do you know her identity?
Nope. Her face was torn up.
No wallet, proof of identity or phone
on the body.
Only a stamp on her arm.
What about fingerprints?
Yes, but we don't have a match.
What are you up to lately?
It must be destiny.
I'm working on this case too.
I'm doing a feature story.
What a coincidence!
If you find anything, let me know.
Of course! We'll swap.
I heard you mention
the girl was here for Ladies Night?
We think so.
That's why we came to see their CCTV
to check for anyone wearing
the victim's clothes
and we'll know what she looked like.
I followed the stamp here.
Why brings you here?
I came with a friend...
to look for someone.
Sorry, YY! You're busy talking,
I need to head home.
I'll let you carry on and I'll get going.
Thank you for your help.
If Emma was the faceless corpse,
after she left home
did she look for Ken at Tender Bar?
That's why she got a new stamp on her arm?
Oh dear, was Emma really in trouble?
Elsa, I just woke up.
Where are you?
Mom, I went grocery shopping.
I'm on my way home now. See you.
Mom, I'm home!
Daddy?
Elsa, you're back!
When I woke up,
you weren't anywhere in the house.
Have you any idea how worried I was?
Sorry, Mom!
I saw you took sleeping pills,
I know you won't be up soon.
I didn't know Daddy would
come home suddenly.
I went out to Tsimshatsui
and bought special ingredients from
a bigger supermarket
so I can cook for you tonight.
That's far away. What did you get?
Blue cheese pasta with cherry tomatoes
and an avocado salad. What do you think?
Elsa, I'll like anything you make for me.
You really want to make avocado salad?
Yes!
You didn't buy avocado.
No avocado?
I'm sure I bought it.
It's OK. We'll like anything you make.
You want to ask me something?
You said last time,
you have a patient who's a CID.
Did you find out the identity of
the female corpse?
Of course I did. But she hasn't called back.
You still think it was Emma?
I makes me uneasy when I think about it.
I just want to make sure.
I better start preparing.
I'll call you when the food is ready.
Should I tell Daddy about
what I overheard at the bar?
If I told him,
he's bound to ask how I found out.
Daddy is too smart.
He'll figure out I snuck over
to the bar again
and that Emma has a secret
boyfriend call Ken.
If Emma is alive,
she wouldn't want him to know.
In case Emma was the faceless corpse,
and the Police can't find her identity,
if I don't tell Daddy Emma and the faceless
corpse have similar features,
then we'll never know what happened to her.
I better tell Daddy...
(Elsa, I have settled down)
(I'm safe, don't worry)
(I'll be in touch later)
It's Emma!
Daddy, look! Emma said she's safe.
You're sneaky.
You're in touch with Emma all along.
You used the name Louise, right?
But didn't tell us.
Sorry, Daddy! As long as Emma is safe...
Go tell Mom!
Mom should be thrilled.
She'll be able to sleep tonight.
Mom...look!
Emma just texted me she's safe.
She's fine. Don't worry!
It's OK!
Elsa, tell Emma for me
I know she's in touch with you.
If she has decided to leave this family,
there's nothing I can do about it.
I won't look for her either.
She knew she'll break her mother's heart,
but she still went ahead and did it.
Tell her she's on her own from now on.
Do I have to do it?
We're cutting her off from now on?
She left us.
Just do it.
I'll pretend I never had
a daughter like her.
You're the only daughter we have
from now on.
OK, I sent it.
I've been thinking...
Now that Emma is gone,
God knows what people she hangs out with.
It's quite dangerous.
She'll eventually get busted.
Then she'll expose you and Mom.
I have decided we should leave
Hong Kong ASAP.
Leave? Where can we go?
You'll know later.
But before we leave,
we must pretend nothing happened.
Don't make anyone suspicious.
If we pack up and leave,
what if Emma wants to come home?
She'll have no home.
I don't think she's coming back.
Elsa, Daddy is right.
We should leave before anything
else happens.
By then, we won't be able to leave.
We might be forced apart.
Elsa, I can't lose you too.
You must come with us.
OK.
Emma, Mom and Daddy are taking me
away from Hong Kong.
I want to see you before I go.
Can you tell me where you are?
I promise I won't tell them.
You won't tell me?
I don't believe you can dodge me.
What's the password?
My birthday and Emma's birthday?
Or the release date of the DSE
we pretended to have taken?
Wrong again!?
Rats! I have one last chance.
Calm down, Hong Ka-yee!
You're close to Emma,
you should know what password she used.
Calm down and think...
OK...I'm in your room now.
Hurry up and leave word for me,
or the limited edition sneakers
will be gone.
It's on, what's the password?
I told you last time,
the day we had our first equestrian lesson.
Do you remember?
Of course I do!
Ken, I found you.
He's in a band as well.
No wonder you guys hit it off.
But so what? You're a scumbag.
When I find Emma,
I'll tell her to ditch Ken.
The key is to persuade Emma to come home.
Then we won't have to leave.
HKIU?
YY went to school there.
Better ask him for help...
If you find anything, let me know.
I'm working on this case too.
I'm doing a feature story.
What if YY found out about me?
He's chummy with the Police.
I'll be asking for trouble.
Forget it. I'll go by myself.
Excuse me...do you know
where can I find people in a band?
You want the band room?
Take these stairs to the West Wing.
I want that...
Want what?
I'm browsing through Instabook
and saw a Joint U Live Band Party.
They said the legendary Band Stud
will be there to jam music.
If I were in the university,
I could have played a song or two with him.
Then I can die with no regrets.
I hope you'll get your chance.
This is Dr. Hong.
Dr. Hong, two officers from the
New Territories East Crime Unit
are waiting downstairs to see you.
No problem. Send them up.
Yes, Dr. Hong.
Come in!
Dr. Hong, these are the officers from
the New Territories East Crime Unit.
Please have a seat.
This way...
Hello, Dr. Hong.
I'm Kwan Zhi-fung of the New Territories
East Crime Unit.
I'm Lee Shun-cheong.
What can I do for you, officers?
Dr. Hong, we came to ask you
about endometriosis or what is
commonly known as chocolate cyst.
We're tracing an oral drug for
chocolate cyst.
This is the one.
We understand this is a new drug
made in Hong Kong
and must be prescribed by
obstetricians and gynecologists.
That's why we wanted to know
how often is this drug prescribed?
Here...got it.
Obstetricians and gynecologists of
this hospital, including me,
over the past six months,
have prescribed this drug to 33 patients.
Can I ask you why you need this information?
It's about a case we're working on.
The recent faceless female corpse.
The autopsy report showed the victim
had a chocolate cyst on the left side
of the pelvic peritoneum.
We found traces of this drug in her blood.
Since there was no proof of identity
on the body,
we're trying to trace the drug.
Dr. Hong, do you remember
prescribing this drug to a patient
who matches the figure of the body?
I might need to read the autopsy report
before I can answer your question.
Can you give us a list of the patients
who have taken this drug?
Sorry, because it involves
the patients' privacy,
the hospital must reach a consensus
before we can respond to your request.
We understand. We'll wait to hear from you.
No problem.
Dr. Hong, we'll excuse ourselves.
Thank you.
Please come this way.
Here...drink some warm water.
See if it'll help.
Emma, hang in there.
Daddy is on his way home.
Emma, how are you?
Daddy brought a new drug.
Take it and you'll feel better.
Water, Emma.
The autopsy report showed the victim
has a chocolate cyst on the left side
of the pelvic peritoneum.
We found traces of this drug in her blood.
Since there was no proof of identity
on the body...
Hello! Are you Ken?
Yes. You are...
I'm Emma's sister.
Emma's sister?
You're Emma Hong's boyfriend,
your name is Ken, right?
Yes...what is it?
I just knew it.
I recognized you from the bar last time.
Emma ran away from home,
that's why you came to see me?
Do you know where she is?
I really want to see her.
Relax! She's in a safe place.
I'll take you to her now.
Great! Thanks!
This way...
Where are you now?
Fung Sir!
We have the result from
the fingerprints database.
Nothing matched the corpse.
We also have the DNA report.
No match either.
It's likely she was an illegal immigrant.
I saw the patient list from Dr. Hong.
Nothing there either.
That's odd. How could an II have access to
a drug prescribed by obstetricians
and gynecologists?
Did she know a doctor who could
pull some strings?
Or she stole them?
Even when there's no match on DNA
or fingerprints,
it doesn't mean she's an II.
Probably someone without an ID card
but somehow managed to live in Hong Kong
such as an overstayer or illegal resident.
We just don't know how she managed
to have access to this drug.
Let's check places where people with
no ID cards usually hang out.
Let's start with brothels
and illegal guest houses.
Here we are!
Come on in...
Thanks.
Emma...
Where's Emma?
You can't be that naive!
What are you doing? Stay back!
Stay back...
Give it back to me, you creep!
Elsa, I'll be home early tonight.
When Mom wakes up,
tell her I have something important
to discuss with you tonight.
Let go of me...
Hello, Elsa?
Are you Elsa's father?
Yes. Who are you?
Want to hear your precious daughter's voice?
Help...Daddy, help me...
Elsa! Elsa, what's wrong?
Where are you, Elsa?
Listen, I want $3M, all in $500 notes.
Before 6 o'clock tonight,
put it next to the garbage can in
the Lok Ping Road park.
No Police. Or you know what will happen.
OK...I'll pay you. Don't hurt Elsa.
Good! No games or you'll never
see her again.
Hello? Hello?
Sir, can I help you?
I wish to withdraw $3M cash.
All in $500 notes.
Did you call in advance?
No.
Sorry, if you didn't call ahead,
we don't have that much cash ready.
I'll take as much as you have.
All set, Mr. Hong.
Thank you.
I just called ahead
to meet with your manager, Mr. Chan.
Mr. Hong, here's $500K.
Thank you.
Sure!
Relax! We'll go to Meow Lung Kee
in a few days
and we're all set.
But I have things to do right now.
Later.
Let go of me...
Don't worry, your rich Daddy will save you.
What have you done to Emma? Where is she?
You said I'm her boyfriend,
what do you think?
Let go of me...